Jason Tieu
304047667

Project 5

Q1: For which communication(s) do you use the SSL encryption? If you are encrypting the communication 
from (1) to (2) in Figure 2, for example, write (1)→(2) in your answer.

The information from (4)->(5) and (5)->(6) was encrypted.

Q2: How do you ensure that the item was purchased exactly at the Buy_Price of that particular item?

I had to store the Buy_Price of the visited item page and make sure the session saves it.